<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- These are the generic names for the app -->
    <string name="app_name">Aquarium</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="back">Back to Ecoscapes Map</string>

    <!-- These are the strings for Tanks -->
    <string name="living_reef">Living Reef</string>
    <string name="artificial_reef">Artificial Reef</string>
    <string name="shark_tank">Cat Shark and Dogfish</string>
    <string name="poison_tank">Poisonous Creatures</string>
    <string name="lobster_tank">Lobster Tank</string>
    <string name="school_tank">Schooling Reef</string>
    <string name="cave_tank">Blind Cave Tank</string>

    <!-- These are strings for individual fish -->
    <string name="catshark">Banded Catshark</string>
    <string name="catshark_desc">The Banded Catfish is a ground shark that lives mostly in the 
        Indo-Pacific waters, from Japan to Australia. They got their name from their barbels
        which look like cat whiskers. They can be distinguished by the wide black stripes that
        appear on their bodies, sometimes with visible brown spots in between as their grow
        bigger. \n\n
        The Banded Catshark needs to be in a very large aquarium with sand substrate because
        it likes to stay in the bottom. It mostly feeds on small crustaceans, mussels, and squid.\n\n</string>
    <string name="dogfish">Smooth Dogfish</string>
    <string name="dogfish_desc">The Smooth Dogfish is a shark within the family of hound sharks.
        They are gray in color, sometimes brown with shades of yellow. They can grow up to about 
        5 feet in length and matures very fast. The female Dogfish can live up to 16 years, but the 
        males are only up to 10 years.\n\n
        The Smooth Dogfish is also called Dusky Smooth-Hound because it is a cunning predator who
        feeds on large crustaceans like shrimps, crabs, and even lobsters. They have flat, blunt teeth
        which are perfect for crushing hard shells of their prey.\n\n</string>
    <string name="spinylobster">Florida Spiny Lobster</string>
    <string name="spinylobster_desc">The Florida Spiny Lobster is also called the Caribbean Spiny Lobster.
        They inhabit the reefs and groves of the western Atlantic Ocean. As its name suggest, this
        lobster\'s body is covered with spines, with two huge ones sticking above their eyestalks.
        Another ineteresing fact is that they have no claws or pincers.\n\n
        The Florida Spiny Lobster\'s diet includes mollusks, sea vegetation, and dead fish. On the other
        hand, they are very vulnerable to predators like sharks and octopuses. Moreover, they are a very
        common seafood item. During the lobster season, they can be found everywhere in the Bahamas
        and the Florida Keys.\n\n</string>
    <string name="slipperlobster">Ridged Slipper Lobster</string>
    <string name="slipperlobster_desc">The Slipper Lobster is a crustacean that inhabits the warm waters
        of the world. The Slipper Lobster is not a real lobster, but are closely related to Spiny
        Lobsters. They are easily recognizable with the two large plates that extend beyond their 
        heads which are one of its antennaes. The other antennae is in between acting as an 
        environment sensor. \n\n
        The Ridged Slipper Lobster got its name because of their highly segmented body. There are six
        segments on their head, six on the abdomen, and eight in the thorax. Their diet includes
        mollusks, oysters, and various echinoderms.\n\n </string>
    <string name="scorpionfish">Spotted Scorpionfish</string>
    <string name="scorpionfish_desc">The Scorpion Fish got its name because of its method of catching food.
        It injects poison through their dorsal fins upon punctiring their prey. Despite their poisonous 
        nature, there are several predators that feed on them including large snappers and morray eels.\n\n
        Scorpion Fishes are found in the Atlantic waters generally near rocks and crevices where they
        wait to ambush an unwary prey. They use camouflage to perfectly hide themselves too. They are
        often found stationary and motionless, even growing algae on their scales sometimes.\n\n </string>
    <string name="toadfish">Gulf Toadfish</string>
    <string name="toadfish_desc">The Gulf Toadfish are species of toadfish native to the Gulf of
        Mexico. They prefer to hang out around shallow water with most baitfish, that is why they are
        often caught in the hooks of anglers. In addition, they will eat chunks of baits especially
        if it is squid or frozen fish.\n\n
        In general, the Guld Toadfish is covered in a slimy substance which makes them unlikable
        by anglers. The Guld Toadfish itself is not very toxic but their slimy skin can cause
        terrible physical irritation.\n\n </string>
    <string name="balloonfish">Balloonfish</string>
    <string name="balloonfish_desc">The Balloonfish is also called Porcupine Fish which are native in
        several parts of the world including the western Atlantic from Florida to Brazil, and all over
        Asia and northern Arustralia. These fishes are related to the Burrfish and there are about 19
        different species of Balloonfish.\n\n
        The Porcupine Fish is recognizable by its spines which are very visible when they are inflated.
        When relaxed, the spines are laid back and ay flat on their bodies. The spines are erect and 
        more visible when they puff themselves to ward off potential predators and enemies.\n\n</string>
    <string name="burrfish">Striped Burrfish</string>
    <string name="burrfish_desc">The Striped Burrfish is also commonly knkown as the Spiny Boxfish. It
        is closely related to the Balloonfish, but has shorter spines and a spherical body. It also
        has several lateral stripes running across its body with a few black spots around the dorsal fin 
        another below the pectoral fin.\n\n
        The mouth of the Burrfish resembles almost a beak with the way its jaw is oriented. They are
        mostly found in the tropics along the Atlantic Coast. Their diet consists of small fish,
        barnacles, snails, and other small crustaceans.\n\n</string>
    <string name="horseconch">Florida Horse Conch</string>
    <string name="horseconch_desc">The Florida Horse Conch is a very large tropical sea snail, which is 
        also called, scientifically, as Triplofusus Giganteus. They are predatory sea snails closely
        related to spindle snails and tulip snails. \n\n
        The Florida Horse Conch is typically orange in color, with a shell that can reach up to 24 inches.
        They spend most of their time in the sand or mud flats. They feed on other larger conch species such
        as the Lightning Whelk and Queen Conch, and sometimes even considered cannibalistic as they
        eat hermit crabs in aquariums.\n\n</string>
    <string name="lookdowns">Lookdowns</string>
    <string name="lookdown_desc">Lookdown fishes are recognizable with their unusual body shape. It is 
        very thin and flat with shimmering blue-gray scales. They also have elongated dorsal and anal fins
        resembling that of a scythe. It also has a weird face with its mouth set low and its eyes high.\n\n
        Lookdowns are found on west Atlantic waters, ranging from Canada down to Florida, even further 
        down up to Uruguay. These are not commercially important but they are considered as a game fish
        for anglers and they are very unique addition to any aquarium.\n\n</string>
    <string name="highhats">High Hat Fish</string>
    <string name="highhats_desc">The High Hat Fish is a small, peaceful fish that can grow up to nine
        inches. Theie body is usually white with dark lateral stripes with an erect dorsal fin. They are
        mostly found in the Atlantic waters and the Gulf of Mexico.\n\n
        The diet of the High Hats include black worms and brine shrimps, sometimes meaty food. They would
        search the sandy bottom of the seafloor or the aquarium to look for worms and small crustaceans.\n\n</string>	
    <string name="blindcave">Blind Cavefish</string>
    <string name="blindcave_desc">The Blind Cave Fish is also called the Mexican Tetra because it is mostly 
        found in deep Mexican caves and in the dark, warm waters of Central America. They can grow up to 
        about 3.5 inches long whiel some grow another inch bigger. They have no pigment in their scales, 
        and so they appear pink-ish in color.\n\n 
        Contrary to its name, the Blind Cave Fish are actually born with normal eyes, which then 
        deteriorates rapidly as they grow older. Their vision deteriorates to the point that that even 
        lose their eyes. They can move sensing water pressure though.\n\n</string>
    <string name="purplereef">Purple Reeffish</string>
    <string name="purplereef_desc">The Purple Reef Fish as its name suggests, is coveered in shimmering
        violet or purple color. They are one of the species of the Damselfish family, also often called
        Indigo Damselfish at times. \n\n
        They inhabit the waters of the Atlantic as well as the Gulf of Mexico. Some sightings extend as
        far as the shores of Mexico and Brazil. They like to hang out in deep, sloped reefs where the male
        is usually found guarding the eggs and hatchlings.\n\n</string>

    <!-- These are for the living reef -->
    <string name="bluetang">Blue Tang</string>
    <string name="bluetang_desc"> The Blue Tang lives in coastal waters, coral reefs, and 
        inshore rocky areas. they can be found in waters ranging from the Northeast United 
        States to the reefs of Brazil. \n\n
        At its early stages, the Blue Tang are yellow with blue spots around its eyes.
        As they mature, The Blue Tang\'s color becomes vibrant blue with bold black markings. 
        The black shade begins at the eyes down to its dorsal fins. It continues down to its tail 
        where it circles back above the pectoral fin to create a unique pattern.\n\n
        The Blue Tang is known to have several other names. Some of which are Blue Doctor, Blue
 		Barber, Palette Surgeonfish, and Regal Tang.\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="doctorfish">Doctorfish Tang</string>
    <string name="doctorfish_desc">The Doctorfish Tang is similar to the Blue Tang but without the vibrant
        blue color. Instead, the Doctorfish Tang has gray-blue scales and light blue fins. The Doctorfish 
        gets its name from the "scalpels" located at their tail. \n\n
        The Doctorfish Tang cn be found in the Atlantic Ocean and in some areas of west Africa. During 
        the day, the Doctorfish Tang spends most of the time looking for algae and plant matter from rocks.
        At night, the Doctorfish Tangs gather in a group to reproduce and spawn baby Tangs. \n\n\n</string>
    <string name="hawkfish">Red-Spotted Hawkfish</string>
    <string name="hawkfish_desc">The Red-Spotted Hawkfish has a white body covered with red spots mostly
        on their head and their dorsal fins. Its body has stripes ranging from black to brown. \n\n
        The Red-Spotted Hawkfish can be found in the waters of the Atlantic, especially in the reefs
        of Florida and Texas. They can also be found in the Caribbean seas and Brazil. The Red-Spotted
        Hawkfish likes rocky areas since they like to hide in crevices. They mostly feed on small
        fishes and shrimp. \n\n\n</string>
    <string name="porkfish">Porkfish</string>
    <string name="porkfish_desc">The Porkfish got its name because of its physical characteristics. It
        has a blunt mouth and thick lips, and its also quite plump. Juvenile porkfishes have white
        scales with yellow marks on its head, dorsal fins, and pelvic fins. Adult porkfishes, however,
        has yellow stripes from its middle section down to its tail fins. \n\n
        The Porkfish can be found in the waters of the Atlantic as well as the Gulf of Mexico. 
        They are often compared to their closely related family, the Burrito Grunt which is found
        in the Pacific.\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="flamefish">Flamefish</string>
    <string name="flamefish_desc">As it name suggests, the Flamefish comes with a fiery red color
        and black spots. They are found in the waters of the west Atlantic Ocean and in the Gulf of
        Mexico. They can also be spotted in the coral reef of Brazil and the Caribbean. \n\n
        The Flamefish can grow up to a maximum of 4.5 inches. They are very common in pet stores
        and are great for new aquariums. They are also known to fight other fishes in groups, that is why
        it is suggested to keep a limited number of Flamefish in one aquarium.\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="angelfish">Pygmy Angelfish</string>
    <string name="angelfish_desc">The Pygmy Angelfish is also called the Cherubfish, Cherub Angelfish, 
        or Atlantic Pygmy Angelfish. It is a brilliant sapphire-blue with orange highlights to the face.\n\n
		The Pygmy Angelfish requires a 55 gallon or larger tank with numerous hiding places and live rock 
		for grazing on microalgae. It may nip at large-polyped stony corals and clam mantles.\n\n
		A breeding pair may be kept, and the Pygmy Angelfish has been bred in an aquarium with success.\n\n</string>
    <string name="fairybass">Fairy Basslet</string>
    <string name="fairybass_desc">The Fairy Basslet comes in a vibrant purple color with shades of yellow,
        red, and orange. They like to stay within coral reefs of Florida and the Caribbean. \n\n
        Although they can only grow up to a maximum of about three inches, Fairy Basslets will fight 
        other fishes, including their own species, when their territory is threatened. They go hunting 
        food in schools, looking for zooplanktons and smaller sea creatures. Usually, the male Basslet
        guards the eggs against predators during the day.</string>
    <string name="slipperydick">Slippery Dick</string>
    <string name="slipperydick_desc">The Slippery Dick is native in the coasts of the Atlantic. They
        are one of the wrasse species, and clad in white scales. They have a distinct later stripe from its 
        head down to the tail, and another faint stripe below that. \n\n
        Similar to all the wrasse species, the Slippery Dick has an ability to change their sex
        depending on biological and environemental factors. These fishes can grow up to 14 inches in length.
        They mostly feed on invertebrates such as crabs, sea urchins, and gastropods.\n\n\n </string>
    <string name="yellowhead">Yellowhead Wrasse</string>
    <string name="yellowhead_desc">The Yellowhead Wrasse is a common species of the wrasse family. They
        are easily identified with their bright yellow color and a lateral blue stripe running from
        their eyes down to the tail fins. Adult yellowhead wrasses change the color of the lower part 
        of their body to brown or black.\n\n
        The Yellowhead wrasse can be found in the Atlantic Ocean, Caribbean Sea, and the Gulf of Mexico.
        They often feed on crabs, shrimps, and sea urchins. Like othre wrasse fishes, the Yellowhead wrasse
        start off as a female and later turn into a male. Mature males are said to be protective, territorial,
        and dominant during breeding season.\n\n</string>
    <string name="turbosnail">Turbo Snail</string>
    <string name="turbosnail_desc">The Turbo Snail is very popular in aquariums because they significantly 
        reduce algae that form inside the tank. The Turbo Snail is also known as Turban, or Top Shell
        Snail. They are native to the waters of California and Mexico.
        For aquarium hobbyists, the Torbo Snail is very handy for cleaning up crevices and holes especially 
        in huge aquariums.\n\n</string>
    <string name="pincushion">Pincushion Urchin</string>
    <string name="pincushion_desc">The Pincushion Urchin is a type or urchin clad with hundreds of spines.
        Its color ranges from mostly purple, red, and blue. During the daytime, they burrow themselves
        in dark crevices and caves. After dark, they come out to eat algae. It is observed that the
        Pincushion Urchin can roam around the entire tank just to graze on algae.</string>
    <string name="redstar">Red Serpent Star</string>
    <string name="redstar_desc">Serpent Stars are often known as Brittle Starfish for their long, slender
        arms and a compact body. Unlike other starfishes, the arms of serpent stars are covered with scales
        not spines. \n\n
        Red Serpent Stars also come in orange and maroon shades. As a result, they are often called Ruby 
        Serpent Stars as well. They are common in the waters of the Caribbean. In the aquarium, their diet
        can be supplemented with chopped meat, shrimp, or mussels.\n\n</string>
    <string name="orangeback">Orangeback Bass</string>
    <string name="orangeback_desc">The Orangeback Bass has some very unique patterns in its scales. Its upper 
        body has a solid orange color, shaded with black as they mature. the lower half of their body comes in 
        yellow hues with alternating patterns of medium-sized and huge spots. \n\n
        The Orangeback Bass can be found in the Atlantic Ocean down to the northern waters of South America.
        They like to swin in crevices between rocks and also along the coral reefs about 100 feet deep.</string>
    <string name="saddlebass">Saddle Bass</string>
    <string name="saddlebass_desc">The Saddle Bass are native to the Atlantic Waters, mainly in the Florida
        Keys and the Yucatan in Mexico. They live in reefs no deeper than 180 meters. they can grow up to
        a maximum of 10 centimeters.\n\n</string>
    <string name="harlequin">Harlequin Bass</string>
    <string name="harlequin_desc">Similar to other species on the Serranus family, the Harlequin Bass has a 
        unique pattern in its scales. They are clad in white color, with varying black patterns scattered 
        around its body. It also has a yellowish belly which makes it more attrative. \n\n
        The Harlequin Bass is a very good beginner fish for new aquariums. It feeds on small crustaceans 
        and shrimps. In addition, it can lso be fed frozen food and chopped meat.\n\n</string>
    <string name="bluehead">Bluehead Wrasse</string>
    <string name="bluehead_desc">The Bluehead Wrasse is a salwater fish found in the coral reefs of the 
        western Atlantic Oceean. Like other wrasse species, the Bluehead Wrasse display varying colors 
        in different life stages. Juveniles usually are yellow with black marks along their side. Adult 
        wrasses develop a black-white-black pattern from its back down to its belly. The pattern separates its
        yellowish body from its blue head.\n\n</string>

    <!-- These are for the artificial reef -->
    <string name="sergeantmajor">Sergeant Major</string>
    <string name="sergeantmajor_desc">The Sergeant Major fish is a small round fish within the species of damselfish.
        Its body color changes depending on the amount of light or depth it is in. When it is near the surface
        of the water, it appears blue and its stripes are very visible. When it hides on the shadows, it appears
        gray with blue hues, and sometimes, the stripes are not clearly seen.\n\n
        The Seargeant Major can be found in the United States, from Rhode Island down to Florida. They are also 
        seen in the coasts of east South America. They are also abundant in the shores of west Africa, especially 
        near Cape Verde.\n\n</string>
    <string name="shogfish">Spanish Hogfish</string>
    <string name="shogfish_desc">The Spanish Hogfish is a species of wrasse, typically found in the coasts of
        the Atlantic. It is abundant in the Gulf of Mexico, the Caribbean, and southern Brazil. \n\n
        The color of the Spanish Hogfish changes as it matures. As a juvenile, it is distinguishable with
        a highlight of purple from its head to halfway of its body. the other half is covered with yellow or gold
        scales. As they grow, their colors becomes brownish-black with a yellow belly.\n\n</string>
    <string name="chogfish">Cuban Hogfish</string>
    <string name="chogfish_desc">Unlike its close relative, the Spanish Hogfish, the Cuban Hogfish retains its
        vibrant color throughout its lifetime. It has an orange to pick coloration, with a distinct yellow shade
        around its top tail fins. \n\n
        The Cuban Hogfish is carnivorous, feeding on small crustaceans such as shrimps and snails. It can also feed 
        on meaty foods like worms, and even shelled creatures such as mussels and clams.\n\n</string>
    <string name="chromis">Blue Chromis</string>
    <string name="chromis_desc">The Blue Chromis is a small, beautiful addition in any aquarium. It can be recognized 
        with its cyan scales, sometimes light blue which slowly fades as green going down to its belly. When the 
        male is prepared to breed, it changes its color to a pale yellow hue. \n\n
        The Blue Chromis is native in western Atlantic Ocean. In aquariums, they are very quiet and non-aggressive. 
        It mostly feeds on meaty foods and herbivore flakes.\n\n</string>
    <string name="clownwrasse">Clown Wrasse</string>
    <string name="clownwrasse_desc">Also known as a Red Coris Wrasse, the Clown Wrasse can be seen everywhere
        in the reefs of the Pacific and Hawaiian seas. Its coloration changes as it grows. At a young age, it is
        similar to a Clown Fish, with an orange body color accented with white spots outlined with balck marks. As 
        it ages, it becomes dark orange with distinct lateral stripes consisting of blue spots.\n\n
        The diet of the Clown Wrasse includes frozen shrimp, marine flakes, and marine pellet food. They are very 
        small and can grow up to a maximum of 1.3 inches.\n\n</string>
    <string name="damsel">Bi-color Damselfish</string>
    <string name="damsel_desc">The Bi-color Damselfish is a bony fish that lives int he rocky reefs of Florida,
        the Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico. It can grow to about 4 inches with large dorsal, pelvic and anal fins.\n\n
        It can be distinguished by its color, mostly dark brown and gray, with a shade of white and yellow at the 
        tail fins. A school of damnsel fish are very territorial and will fight to defend their rocky home.\n\n </string>

    <!-- These are for the corals -->


    <!-- These are for the fragments and activites -->
    <string name="title_activity_shark_tank">Shark Tank</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lobster_tank">Lobster Tank</string>
    <string name="title_activity_poison_tank">Poisonous Creatures</string>
    <string name="title_activity_school_tank">Schooling Reef</string>
    <string name="title_activity_living_reef">Living Reef</string>
    <string name="title_activity_artificial_reef">Artificial Reef</string>
    <string name="title_activity_blind_cave_tank">Cave Tank</string>

</resources>